Register of the Firing Line (Television Program) broadcast records 80040.4089238
Hoover Institution Archives
- Production Materials File, 1966-1994 (Boxes 1-69, 193)
  - Speaker and research files, 1966-1999 (Boxes 16-69)
    - Ky, Nguyen Cao, September 14, 1975 (Box-folder 47: 9)
    - Lambertson, Giles; Sobran, Joseph, October 1, 1990 (Box-folder 47: 10)
    - Ledeen, Michael; Kinsley, Michael, September 3, 1985 (Box-folder 47: 11)
    - Lee Kuan Yew, October 30, 1978 (Box-folder 48: 1)
    - Lehrman, Lewis; Martin, Preston, January 9, 1986 (Box-folder 48: 2)
    - Lehrman, Lewis, December 10, 1981 (Box-folder 48: 3)
    - Lehrman, John; Nunn, Sam; Westmoreland, William Childs, September 18, 1981 (Box-folder 48: 4)
    - Lejackman, Robert, October 1, 1979 (Box-folder 48: 5)
    - Lelyveld, Joseph; Hutchinson, John, November 7, 1985 (Box-folder 48: 6)
    - Lemann, Nicholas, April 9, 1991 (Box-folder 48: 7)
    - Lerner, Max, December 30, 1987 (Box-folder 48: 8)
    - Lerner, Max; Bern, Walter, November 7, 1988 (Box-folder 48: 9)
    - Levy, David, March 26, 1992 (Box-folder 48: 10)
    - Lewis, Anthony, March 10, 1978 (Box-folder 48: 11)
    - Lewis, Anthony, March 30, 1981 (Box-folder 48: 12)
    - Lewis, Anthony; Greenfield, Jeff, February 25, 1985 (Box-folder 49: 1)
    - Lewis, Anthony; Clurman, Richard; Borchgrave, Arnaud de, December 11, 1986 (Box-folder 49: 2)
    - Lewis, Anthony, November 4, 1991 (Box-folder 49: 3)
    - Lidoy, G. Gordon, January 11, 1978 (Box-folder 49: 4)
    - Limbaugh, Rush, September 16, 1992 (Box-folder 49: 5)
    - Lind, William; Hadley, Arthur, July 23, 1986 (Box-folder 49: 6)
    - Livingstone, Ken, September 16, 1986 (Box-folder 49: 7)
    - Lofton, John; Phillips, Howard, June 24, 1987 (Box-folder 49: 8)
    - London, Herb; Rinfret, Pierre, July 10, 1990 (Box-folder 49: 9)
    - Lord, Winston, March 1, 1982 (Box-folder 49: 10)
    - Lowenstein, Allard, December 7, 1973 (Box-folder 49: 11)
    - Lowenstein, Allard, April 11, 1975 (Box-folder 49: 12)
    - Lowenstein, Allard; Pfeffer, Leo, August 2, 1976 (Box-folder 49: 13)
    - Lowenstein, Allard; Solarz, Stephen J., June 15, 1979 (Box-folder 50: 1)
    - Lowenstein, Hubertus Zu; Livingston, Robert, May 13, 1982 (Box-folder 50: 2)
    - Lugar, Richard, February 14, 1980 (Box-folder 50: 3)
    - Lukacs, John; Haag, Ernest van den, July 12, 1984 (Box-folder 50: 4)
    - Lukacs, John, January 18, 1982 (Box-folder 50: 5)
    - Machan, Tibor, April 2, 1982 (Box-folder 50: 6)
    - Magnet, Myron, September 22, 1993 (Box-folder 50: 7)
    - Mahoney, J. Daniel; Green, Mark; Greenfield, Jeff, July 7, 1983 (Box-folder 50: 8)
    - Mailer, Norman, October 11, 1979 (Box-folder 50: 9)
    - Malarkey, Thomas; Navin, Hank, June 2, 1983 (Box-folder 50: 10)
    - Mandy, S. Nigel; Solarz, Stephen; Neuhaus, Richard, September 6, 1985 (Box-folder 50: 11)
    - Mankiewicz, Hank, September 22, 1972 (Box-folder 50: 12)
    - Mankiewicz, Hank, September 22, 1972 (Box-folder 50: 13)
    - Manning, Bayless; Bundy, William, June 15, 1977 (Box-folder 51: 1)
    - Mannix, Arthur J. Jr.; Moskowitz, Richard; Rosenblatt, Stanley, M., May 3, 1983 (Box-folder 51: 2)
    - "Marijuana and the Law" Kaplan, John; Kleindienst, Richard, September 3, 1970 (Box-folder 51: 3)
    - "Marijuana Reconsidered" Grinspoon, Lester; McKinney, Lawrence, June 30, 1971 (Box-folder 51: 4)
    - "Marijuana Laws" Greenwa, John; Bryant, Thomas, December 21, 1972 (Box-folder 51: 6)
    - Mahoney, Daniel; Gottfried, Richard, June 15, 1977 (Box-folder 51: 7)
    - Novak, William; Rosenthal, Mitchell, May 9, 1980 (Box-folder 51: 8)
    - Martin, David; Sanders, Sol, January 15, 1991 (Box-folder 51: 9)
    - Martin, Malachi, December 7, 1973 (Box-folder 51: 10)
    - Martin, Malachi, September 6, 1978 (Box-folder 51: 11)
    - Mathias, Charles McCurdy, March 16, 1978 (Box-folder 52: 1)
    - Mathias, Charles McCurdy, September 18, 1981 (Box-folder 52: 2)
    - Matthews, Tom; Cgapin, Schyler, July 10, 1990 (Box-folder 52: 3)
    - McBrien, Richard; Fox, Thomas, August 2, 1995 (Box-folder 52: 3)
    - McCarthy, Eugene; Etzione, Amitai, May 9, 1984 (Box-folder 52: 4)
    - McCarthy, Eugene, May 9, 1974 (Box-folder 52: 5)
    - McGinniss, Joe; Sadoff, Robert; Halleck, Seymour, December 1, 1983 (Box-folder 52: 6)
    - McGinniss, Joe; Abrams, Floyd, September 18, 1987 (Box-folder 52: 7)
    - Mehdi, M.T.; Perlmutter, Amos, November 4, 1982 (Box-folder 52: 8)
    - Melman, Yossi; Raviv, Dan, July 24, 1990 (Box-folder 53: 1)
    - Menninger, W. Walter; Spring, Raymond L.; Modlin, Herbert, April 19, 1984 (Box-folder 53: 2)
    - Menhuin, Yehudi, April 2, 1986 (Box-folder 53: 3)
    - Metzenbaum, Howard M., June 29, 1979 (Box-folder 53: 4)
    - Meyer, Cord; Snepp, Frank, December 4, 1980 (Box-folder 53: 5)
    - Michener, James A., November 10, 1983 (Box-folder 53: 6)
    - Millr, Arthur, November 22, 1971 (Box-folder 53: 7)
    - Miller, James C. III; Biller, Moe, September 27, 1988 (Box-folder 53: 8)
    - Millett, Kate; Farber, Seth, June 6, 1990 (Box-folder 53: 9)
    - Minogue, Kenneth, Aprill 11, 1985 (Box-folder 53: 10)
    - Minow, Newton, January 8, 1992 (Box-folder 53: 11)
    - Mish, Frederick, July 27, 1993 (Box-folder 53: 12)
    - Morse, Robetr S., January 18, 1979 (Box-folder 53: 13)
    - Mosher, Steven, October 9, 1990 (Box-folder 53: 14)
    - Moss, Robert, March 8, 1977 (Box-folder 53: 15)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P., January 18, 1973 (Box-folder 54: 1)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P., January 16, 1976 (Box-folder 54: 2)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P., September 23, 1977 (Box-folder 54: 3)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P., December 13, 1990 (Box-folder 54: 4)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P., February 14, 1980 (Box-folder 54: 5)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P., August 15, 1980 (Box-folder 54: 6)
    - Mroczyk, Peter, July 8, 1987 (Box-folder 54: 7)
    - Muggeridge, Malcolm, August 20, 1973 (Box-folder 54: 8)
    - Muggeridge, Malcolm, February 5, 1975 (Box-folder 54: 9)
    - Muggeridge, Malcolm, June 27, 1978 (Box-folder 54: 10)
    - Muggeridge, Malcolm, May 21, 1979 (Box-folder 54: 11)
    - Muggeridge, Malcolm, September 14, 1986 (Box-folder 54: 12)
    - Muggeridge, Malcolm, June 27, 1978 (Box-folder 55: 1)
    - Muggeridge, Malcolm, September 6, 1980 (Box-folder 55: 2)
    - Muggeridge, Malcolm, September 6, 1980 (Box-folder 55: 3)
    - Muggeridge, Malcolm, February 19, 1984 (Box-folder 55: 4)
    - Murray, Charles, January 28, 1984 (Box-folder 55: 5)
    - Murray, Charles, November 7, 1988 (Box-folder 55: 6)
    - Nahas, Gabriel; Trebach, Arnold, May 22, 1985 (Box-folder 55: 7)
    - Navarro, Anthony, July 15, 1981 (Box-folder 55: 8)
    - Navasky, Victor, December 4, 1980 (Box-folder 55: 9)
    - Neier, Arych; Dershowitz, Alan; Haag, Ernest van den, July 20, 1978 (Box-folder 56: 1)
    - Netanyahu, Benjamin; Kemoularia, Claude de, May 30, 1986 (Box-folder 56: 2)
    - Neuhaus, Richard John, September 18, 1984 (Box-folder 56: 3)
    - Neuhaus, Richard John, January 12, 1993 (Box-folder 56: 4)
    - Neuhaus, Richard John; Fried, Charles, July 24, 1990 (Box-folder 56: 5)
    - Neuhaus, Richard John, December 10, 1987 (Box-folder 56: 6)
    - Neuhaus, Richard John; Spong, John S., June 8, 1988 (Box-folder 56: 7)
    - Newfield, Jack; DeBrul, Paul; Starr, Roger (Box-folder 56: 8)
    - Niemeyer, Gerhart; McInerny, Ralph; Solomon, W. David, January 6, 1984 (Box-folder 56: 9)
    - "Richard Nixon and Young Conservatives" Smith, J. Bryan; Harroff, Mark; Rohrabacher, Dana; Hukari, Harvey, June 16, 1972 (Box-folder 56: 10)
    - Noonan, Peggy, November 30, 1992 (Box-folder 56: 11)
    - North, James; Chettle, John, April 1, 1985 (Box-folder 56: 12)
    - Norton, Eleanor Holmes, July 15, 1991 (Box-folder 56: 13)
    - Norton, Howard; Smith, Liz; Hentoff, Nat, July 8, 1976 (Box-folder 56: 14)
    - Novak, Micahel; Halbert, John K., June 12, 1981 (Box-folder 57: 1)
    - Novak, Michael; Weigel, George, May 27, 1987 (Box-folder 57: 2)
    - Novak, Michael; McBrien, Richard, February 29, 1988 (Box-folder 57: 3)
    - Nuland, Sherwin, November 1, 1989 (Box-folder 57: 4)
    - O'Beirne, Kate Walsh; Fliegel, Sy, October 1, 1990 (Box-folder 57: 5)
    - O'Brien, Darcy; Watkins, John G., November 12, 1985 (Box-folder 57: 6)
    - Ogburn, Charlton; Charney, Maurice, December 11, 1984 (Box-folder 57: 7)
    - O'Hare, Joseph A.; Steinfels, Peter, October 11, 1979 (Box-folder 57: 8)
    - O'Keefe, Sean, March 30, 1993 (Box-folder 57: 9)
    - "OPEC" Adelman, M. A.; Spriggs, Dillard P., April 11, 1979 (Box-folder 57: 10)
    - Osnos, Peter; Haag, Ernest van den, November 4, 1991 (Box-folder 57: 11)
    - Ossa, Nena; Birns, Laurence; Geyer, Georgie Ann, April 25, 1977 (Box-folder 57: 12)
    - O'Sullivan, John; Pilpel, Harriet, November 28, 1988 (Box-folder 57: 13)
    - O'Sullivan, John; Brookhiser, Richard, November 4, 1992 (Box-folder 57: 14)
    - O'Sullivan, John; Sobran, Joseph, January 26, 1993 (Box-folder 57: 15)
    - Owen, David, July 25, 1977 (Box-folder 58: 1)
    - "The Ozone Controversy" Peterson, Russell W.; McElroy, Michael S.; Scorer, Richard S., July 9, 1975 (Box-folder 58: 2)
    - "Panama and the U.S." Lakas, Demetrio, September 30, 1976 (Box-folder 58: 3)
    - Panama Canal debate, July 13, 1978 (Box-folder 58: 4)
    - Panama Canal I, circa 1977 (Box-folder 58: 5)
    - Panamal Canal II, circa 1977 (Box-folder 58: 6)
    - Pataki, George E., August 2, 1995 (Box-folder 58: 7)
    - Paton, Alan, May 12, 1977 (Box-folder 58: 8)
    - Paul, Ron, January 19, 1988 (Box-folder 58: 9)
    - Pelaez, Emmanuel, October 26, 1986 (Box-folder 58: 10)
    - "The Pentagon Papers" Ellsberg, Daniel, July 25, 1972 (Box-folder 59: 1)
    - Perle, Richard; Hyland, William, January 7, 1988 (Box-folder 59: 2)
    - Perlmutter, Nathan; Fern, Leonard, July 20, 1980 (Box-folder 59: 3)
    - Peters, Charles; Kinsley, Michael, January 13, 1985 (Box-folder 59: 4)
    - Peterson, Peter, June 17, 1981 (Box-folder 59: 5)
    - Peterson, Peter, December 9, 1982 (Box-folder 59: 6)
    - "The Future of Philanthropy" Hunter, David R.; Lyman, Richard W.; Marting, Leeda P., April 29, 1982 (Box-folder 59: 7)
    - Pickens, T. Boone, September 20, 1990 (Box-folder 59: 8)
    - Pilpel, Harriet; Jordan, June, August 26, 1976 (Box-folder 59: 9)
    - Pilpel, Harriet; Harrington, Donald; Davidson, Jim, February 24, 1981 (Box-folder 60: 1)
    - Pilpel, Harriet; Guggenheim, Martin, December 1, 1983 (Box-folder 60: 2)
    - Pilpel, Harriet; Dworkin, Andrea, February 25, 1985 (Box-folder 60: 3)
    - Pilpel, Harriet; Haag, Ernest van den, December 11, 1986 (Box-folder 60: 4)
    - Pinera, Jose, April 28, 1988 (Box-folder 60: 5)
    - Pinker, Steven, July 11, 1995 (Box-folder 60: 6)
    - Pipes, Daniel; Hauser, Rita, June 26, 1991 (Box-folder 60: 7)
    - Pipes, Richard, December 9, 1982 (Box-folder 60: 8)
    - Pipes, Richard, December 13, 1990 (Box-folder 60: 9)
    - Pipes, Richard, September 17, 1991 (Box-folder 60: 10)
    - Pitts, Frank, January 11, 1982 (Box-folder 60: 11)
    - Podhoretz, Norman, November 4, 1992 (Box-folder 60: 12)
    - Podhoretz, Norman, November 29, 1979 (Box-folder 60: 13)
    - Pope, Carl; Quenon, Robert H., October 9, 1990 (Box-folder 60: 14)
    - Powell, Enoch, October 20, 1970 (Box-folder 60: 15)
    - Powell, Enoch, February 20, 1984 (Box-folder 60: 16)
    - Powell, James; Bryant, John, October 11, 1988 (Box-folder 60: 17)
    - Powers, Thomas, March 26, 1980 (Box-folder 60: 18)
    - Prichard, Edward F. Jr., October 27, 1982 (Box-folder 61: 1)
    - Pressler, Larry; Rockefeller, Percy; Robertson, Pat; Shakespeare, Frank, April 27, 1981 (Box-folder 61: 2)
    - Purcell, Susan Kaufman; Roett, Riordan, August 24, 1988 (Box-folder 61: 3)
    - Ramus, Orestes Jr.; Agrait, Luis; Camach, Luis, September 25, 1978 (Box-folder 61: 4)
    - Rabin, Yitzhak, May 9, 1975 (Box-folder 61: 5)
    - Rae, Bob, January 19, 1992 (Box-folder 61: 6)
    - Raviteh, Diane; Cheney, Lynne, September 18, 1987 (Box-folder 61: 7)
    - Reagan, Ronald, July 15, 1971 (Box-folder 61: 8)
    - Reagan, Ronald, January 14, 1980 (Box-folder 61: 9)
    - Recchia, Richard D., January 26, 1993 (Box-folder 61: 10)
    - Reeves, Richard, December 10, 1945 (Box-folder 61: 11)
    - Reeves, Thomas; Lee, Robert E., July 15, 1982 (Box-folder 61: 12)
    - Reich, Otto; Alzugaray, Manuael A., September 3, 1985 (Box-folder 61: 13)
    - Reich, Robert B., July 7, 1983 (Box-folder 61: 14)
    - Reich, Robert; Lekachman, Robert, June 1, 1987 (Box-folder 62: 1)
    - Remnick, David, November 29, 1994 (Box-folder 62: 2)
    - Reid, James, February 14, 1975 (Box-folder 62: 3)
    - Revel, Jean-Francois, November 15, 1984 (Box-folder 62: 4)
    - "Resolved: That Affirmative Action Goals for Minorities and Women Should Be Abolished,", October 13, 1983 (Box-folder 62: 5)
    - Richardson, Elliot, May 26, 1971 (Box-folder 62: 6)
    - Richardson, Elliot, December 20, 1973 (Box-folder 62: 7)
    - Richardson, Heather, March 30, 1993 (Box-folder 62: 8)
    - Richardson, Heather, March 30, 1993 (Box-folder 62: 9)
    - Rivlin, Alice, November 4, 1992 (Box-folder 62: 10)
    - Roberts, Paul Craig; Malkiel, Burton, March 31, 1980 (Box-folder 62: 11)
    - Rocard, Michael, February 23, 1984 (Box-folder 62: 12)
    - Roche, George, November 29, 1979 (Box-folder 62: 13)
    - Roche, George, May 21, 1991 (Box-folder 63: 1)
    - Rohatyn, Felix, July 21, 1982 (Box-folder 63: 2)
    - Rostow, Eugene, September 22, 1993 (Box-folder 63: 3)
    - Rostow, Walt W., September 1, 1971 (Box-folder 63: 4)
    - Rostow, Walt W., February 22, 1983 (Box-folder 63: 4)
    - Rowny, Edward L., December 1, 1986 (Box-folder 63: 5)
    - Ruckelhaus, William, November 12, 1973 (Box-folder 63: 6)
    - Rumsfeld, Donald, October 9, 1975 (Box-folder 63: 7)
    - Rurarz, Zidzslaw, April 15, 1982 (Box-folder 63: 8)
    - Rusher, William A., March 25, 1981 (Box-folder 63: 9)
    - Rusher, William A.; Miller, Howard, September 10, 1981 (Box-folder 63: 10)
    - Rusher, William A.; Leach, Jim, September 6, 1984 (Box-folder 63: 11)
    - Rutler, George; Smith, William, December 6, 1984 (Box-folder 63: 12)
    - Ryan, Allan Jr.; Zumbakis, S. Paul, February 24, 1987 (Box-folder 63: 13)
    - Salisbory, Harrison E., January 30, 1978 (Box-folder 63: 14)
    - Salonen, Neil Albert; Kaufman, Ben L., January 3, 1977 (Box-folder 64: 1)
    - "The SALT Agreements,", July 9, 1972 (Box-folder 64: 2)
    - "Resolved: That the SALT Talks Are in the Interest of U.S. Security,", September 19, 1978 (Box-folder 64: 3)
    - Scali, John; Frederick, Pauline, September 4, 1974 (Box-folder 64: 4)
    - Scheer, Robert; Kinsley, Michael, January 5, 1983 (Box-folder 64: 5)
    - Seignious, George M., August 16, 1979 (Box-folder 64: 6)
    - Walters, Vernon, May 31, 1978 (Box-folder 64: 7)
    - Walters, Vernon, May 27, 1987 (Box-folder 65: 1)
    - Walters, Vernon, January 8, 1992 (Box-folder 65: 2)
    - Walters, Vernon, January 12, 1993 (Box-folder 65: 3)
    - War Crimes, Part I, July 7, 1971 (Box-folder 65: 4)
    - War Crimes, Part II, July 7, 1971 (Box-folder 65: 5)
    - "Conservatives and Watergate,", June 20, 1973 (Box-folder 65: 6)
    - "Resolved: The Watergate Investigation Has Been Vindicated,", November 26, 1973 (Box-folder 65: 7)
    - Watson, Jack H., May 15, 1980 (Box-folder 65: 8)
    - Wattleton, Faye, August 23, 1989 (Box-folder 65: 9)
    - Weidenbaum, Murray; Wise, Robert E. Jr., October 9, 1990 (Box-folder 65: 10)
    - Wennbergg, John E., March 30, 1993 (Box-folder 65: 11)
    - Weinberger, Caspar, March 30, 1973 (Box-folder 66: 1)
    - Weinberger, Caspar, June 2, 1986 (Box-folder 66: 2)
    - Weinberger, Caspar, October 14, 1987 (Box-folder 66: 3)
    - Weinberger, Caspar, June 2, 1989 (Box-folder 66: 4)
    - Weinstein, Allen; Theoharis, Athan, March 21, 1978 (Box-folder 66: 5)
    - Wellstood, Dick; Taylor, Billy, December 9, 1980 (Box-folder 66: 6)
    - Welty, Eudora; Percy, Walker, December 12, 1972 (Box-folder 66: 7)
    - Westin, Alan; Green, Ronald M., March 30, 1981 (Box-folder 66: 8)
    - Westmoreland, William C., January 23, 1976 (Box-folder 66: 9)
    - Westmoreland, William C., September 20, 1979 (Box-folder 66: 10)
    - White, Mark, November 1, 1985 (Box-folder 67: 1)
    - White, Shelby, January 12, 1993 (Box-folder 67: 2)
    - Wicker, Tom; Safire, William, March 10, 1975 (Box-folder 67: 3)
    - The Whiffenpoofs, February 26, 1985 (Box-folder 67: 4)
    - Williams, Edward Bennett, May 3, 1974 (Box-folder 67: 5)
    - Williams, Shirley, circa 1973 (Box-folder 67: 6)
    - Williams, Shirley, December 6, 1973 (Box-folder 67: 7)
    - Williams, Walter; Solarz, Stephen, September 15, 1983 (Box-folder 67: 8)
    - Wills, Garry, January 10, 1973 (Box-folder 67: 9)
    - Wilson, Harold, May 13, 1983 (Box-folder 68: 1)
    - Wilson, James Q., November 14, 1975 (Box-folder 68: 2)
    - Wilson, James Q., September 22, 1993 (Box-folder 68: 3)
    - Wilson, Pete; Maddy, Ken, September 14, 1977 (Box-folder 68: 4)
    - Winspinger, William, March 2, 1982 (Box-folder 68: 5)
    - Wolfe, Tom, December 17, 1970 (Box-folder 68: 6)
    - Wolfe, Tom, July 9, 1975 (Box-folder 68: 7)
    - Wolfe, Tom, October 1, 1981 (Box-folder 68: 8)
    - Wolfe, Tom, January 17, 1990 (Box-folder 68: 9)
    - "Resolved: Women Have It At Least as Good as Men,", November 30, 1982 (Box-folder 68: 10)
    - Woodward, Bob; Bernstein, Carl, July 9, 1974 (Box-folder 68: 11)
    - Worthington, Peter, August 22, 1978 (Box-folder 69: 1)
    - Wriston, Walter, May 30, 1986 (Box-folder 69: 2)
    - Young Americans for Freedom (YAF) Directors, August 15, 1975 (Box-folder 69: 3)
    - YAF, August 29, 1977 (Box-folder 69: 4)
    - Quare Universitas, May 31, 1985 (Box-folder 69: 5)
    - Yergin, Daniel, January 8, 1991 (Box-folder 69: 6)
    - Zemsky, Robert, June 11, 1993 (Box-folder 69: 7)
    - Zielinziger, Michael; Herman, Dick; Yepson, Dare, April 18, 1984 (Box-folder 69: 8)
    - Zion, Sidney; Hinkle, Warren; Rumsfeld, Donald, January 13, 1969 (Box-folder 69: 9)
    - Zion, Sidney; Zogby, James, January 19, 1988 (Box-folder 69: 10)
    - Zion, Sidney; Zogby, James, June 26, 1991 (Box-folder 69: 11)
    - Zumwalt, Elmo R. Jr., May 14, 1976 (Box-folder 69: 12)
- Audiovisual File, 1966-1999 (Boxes 194-410, 352 linear feet)
  - Sound recordings, 1966-1971 (Boxes 194-200, 409-410)
    Sound recordings are the sound tracks of the Firing Line television shows, on open reel tapes and compact sound cassettes. The tapes are of the hour-long shows for commercial television with incomplete coverage of shows 2-240.
    Arranged by show number, though not all shows will have a sound recording.
    - 40-41, 45-47, 49, 51-52, 56-62, 65-67, 70-72 (Box 194)
    - 76-79, 82, 84-85, 90-99, 102-107 (Box 195)
    - 108-132 (Box 196)
    - 133-147, 149-150 (Box 197)
    - 150-155, 157-165 (Box 198)
    - 166-180 (Box 199)
    - 180-195 (Box 200)
    - 196-211 (Box 409)
    - 64, 65, 100-101, 212-226, 227-240 (Box 410)
  - Motion picture film (Film shelf)
    - "Conservative Mr. Buckley," 16mm film
  - Videorecordings, 1966-1999 (Boxes 201-408, 352 linear feet)
    Includes the original broadcast videotapes from Firing Line. Formats include 2-inch quad, 1-inch, 3/4-inch U-matic, Betacam SP, VHS, and S-VHS tapes. Reformatted programs can be viewed on Hoover's digital collections website or on-site in the reading room, or purchased from Amazon. videotapes of programs that have not been reformatted cannot be viewed at this time. Contact the Hoover Institution Archives at hoover_visuals@stanford.edu for more information.